[{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664572259,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":77983,"timeElapsed":503597},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664623370,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":51120,"timeElapsed":554709},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664650778,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":27404,"timeElapsed":582117},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664687311,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":36542,"timeElapsed":618650},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664718187,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":30874,"timeElapsed":649526},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664728356,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":10167,"timeElapsed":659695},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664828302,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":99969,"timeElapsed":759641},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664840377,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":12073,"timeElapsed":771716},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664847537,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":7157,"timeElapsed":778876},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664875438,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":25541,"timeElapsed":806777},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664883646,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8206,"timeElapsed":814985},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664894336,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":10699,"timeElapsed":825675},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664907995,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":13656,"timeElapsed":839334},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664920477,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":12480,"timeElapsed":851816},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664925305,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":4826,"timeElapsed":856644},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664928729,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3422,"timeElapsed":860068},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664931588,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2857,"timeElapsed":862927},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664934478,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2888,"timeElapsed":865817},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665040988,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":104718,"timeElapsed":972327},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665062711,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":21720,"timeElapsed":994049},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665083509,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":20803,"timeElapsed":1014848},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665115636,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":32124,"timeElapsed":1046975},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665149143,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":33513,"timeElapsed":1080482},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665280159,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":131030,"timeElapsed":1211498},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665297189,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":17027,"timeElapsed":1228527},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665324752,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":27561,"timeElapsed":1256091},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665332654,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7900,"timeElapsed":1263993},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665340817,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"110","question":"What are you most afraid of being asked? What are you afraid of other people knowing about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8168,"timeElapsed":1272156},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665370446,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":27967,"timeElapsed":1301785},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665385729,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":15281,"timeElapsed":1317067},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665487850,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":102137,"timeElapsed":1419189},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665496070,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8218,"timeElapsed":1427409},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665563825,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":67762,"timeElapsed":1495164},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665577968,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":14142,"timeElapsed":1509307},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665590466,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":12496,"timeElapsed":1521805},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665598699,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":8231,"timeElapsed":1530038},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665608176,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":9482,"timeElapsed":1539515},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665615815,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":7637,"timeElapsed":1547154},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665647489,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":29638,"timeElapsed":1578828},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665660301,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":12810,"timeElapsed":1591640},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665679793,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":19498,"timeElapsed":1611132},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665687089,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":7294,"timeElapsed":1618428},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665700231,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":13140,"timeElapsed":1631570},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665736534,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":36309,"timeElapsed":1667873},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665750801,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":14265,"timeElapsed":1682140},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665761708,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":10905,"timeElapsed":1693047},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665771662,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":9951,"timeElapsed":1703001},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665791674,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":18528,"timeElapsed":1723013},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665803292,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":11624,"timeElapsed":1734631},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665816919,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":13624,"timeElapsed":1748258},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665824558,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":7637,"timeElapsed":1755897},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665836557,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":11997,"timeElapsed":1767896},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665844951,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":8391,"timeElapsed":1776290},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665884768,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":39823,"timeElapsed":1816107},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665887846,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3075,"timeElapsed":1819185},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665892073,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":4225,"timeElapsed":1823412},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665904722,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":11529,"timeElapsed":1836061},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665909596,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":4871,"timeElapsed":1840935},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665976973,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":67391,"timeElapsed":1908312},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665986333,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":9357,"timeElapsed":1917672},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665997690,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":11356,"timeElapsed":1929029},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666001298,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":3605,"timeElapsed":1932637},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666004907,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3608,"timeElapsed":1936246},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666010504,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":5594,"timeElapsed":1941843},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666013236,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2730,"timeElapsed":1944575},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666027552,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":13046,"timeElapsed":1958891},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666031879,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":4325,"timeElapsed":1963218},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666036837,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":4955,"timeElapsed":1968175},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666042669,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":5836,"timeElapsed":1974008},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666094911,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":52240,"timeElapsed":2026250},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666100382,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":5474,"timeElapsed":2031721},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666108070,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":7686,"timeElapsed":2039409},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666112414,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":4342,"timeElapsed":2043753},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666119412,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":6996,"timeElapsed":2050751},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666141368,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":20795,"timeElapsed":2072707},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666146099,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4729,"timeElapsed":2077438},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666152913,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":6812,"timeElapsed":2084251},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666158126,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":5216,"timeElapsed":2089465},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666170579,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":12450,"timeElapsed":2101918},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666186018,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":15436,"timeElapsed":2117357},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666198174,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":12154,"timeElapsed":2129513},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666214753,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":16577,"timeElapsed":2146092},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666217687,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2938,"timeElapsed":2149026},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666234965,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":15920,"timeElapsed":2166303},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666240308,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":5342,"timeElapsed":2171647},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666247231,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":6921,"timeElapsed":2178570},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666254261,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":7027,"timeElapsed":2185599},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666268980,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":14717,"timeElapsed":2200319},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666272465,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3483,"timeElapsed":2203804},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666280913,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":8452,"timeElapsed":2212252},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666287320,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":6405,"timeElapsed":2218659},{"subjectID":"ojc8fdsqc9","prolificID":"666d97ca3efe7fbd33436995","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ef59d62d8af7a4c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666293460,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":6138,"timeElapsed":2224799}]